<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Recipes on Scott O'Brien</title><link>https://www.scottyob.com/recipes/</link><description>Recent content in Recipes on Scott O'Brien</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><atom:link href="https://www.scottyob.com/recipes/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Butternut carrot soup</title><link>https://www.scottyob.com/recipes/butternut-carrot-soup/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.scottyob.com/recipes/butternut-carrot-soup/</guid><description>Ingredients 1 medium butternut squash sliced in half and seeds scooped out 2 large carrots chopped into large pieces 1 head garlic 1 shallot halved and skin removed 1 tablespoons olive oil 1/2 cup milk or coconut milk 1-2 cups chicken or vegetable stock Light sprinkle of Chili Flakes Method Preheat oven to 425 Put halves of squash face down with other vegetables (garlic in it&amp;rsquo;s own foil). Bake for 50-60 minutes until tender Remove from oven, put into blender with remaining ingredients and Brrrrr.</description></item><item><title>Simple Eggplant Curry</title><link>https://www.scottyob.com/recipes/eggplant-curry/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.scottyob.com/recipes/eggplant-curry/</guid><description>Ingredients 1 eggplant 2 Tbsp olive oil 1 shallot (finely chopped, 1/2 cup) 3 cloves garlic minces 2 tsp garam masala 1 tsp cumin 1 tsp coriander 1 tsp smoked paprika 1 tsp salt 1 can coconut milk (400g, 14oz) 1 can diced tomatoes (400g, 14oz) Service with Rice &amp;amp; Cilantro Method Start cooking rice Cut eggplant into bite-sized cubes. Heat oil in a large pan, cook eggplant until begins to brown (~5 minutes) Add shallot and garlic to the pan, cook for 2 minutes Add spices, coat add cans (tomatoes undrained).</description></item><item><title>Sourdough Naan</title><link>https://www.scottyob.com/recipes/sourdough-naan/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.scottyob.com/recipes/sourdough-naan/</guid><description>Ingredients Wet:
1 cup of sourdough discard (~ 270g) 1/2 cup warm milk (~123g) 1/4 cup plain greek yogurt (~61g, I used honey vanilla, was yum) Dry:
2 cups all purpose flour (~240g) pinch of salt (10g) 1tsp baking powder Method in a big bowl, mix wet ingredients add in dry ingredients Use a fork to really mix into a shaggy mess. I like to scrape down the sides Let sit for ~3 hours Turn out and kneed on a flowered bench, cut into 8 pieces (half, half, half) Melt a generous (4tsp) butter in the microwave.</description></item><item><title>Spag Bol</title><link>https://www.scottyob.com/recipes/spag-bol/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.scottyob.com/recipes/spag-bol/</guid><description>Ingredients 1 1/2 tbsp olive oil 2 garlic cloves , minced 1 onion , finely chopped (brown, yellow or white) 1 lb / 500g beef mince (ground beef) OR half pork, half beef 1/2 cup (125 ml) dry red wine (sub water or beef broth/stock) 2 beef bouillon cubes , crumbled OR 2 tsp granulated beef bouillon (no water, just the powder) 800g / 28 oz can crushed tomato (or tomato passata) 2 tbsp tomato paste 2 tsp white sugar , if needed (Note 3) 2 tsp Worcestershire sauce 2 dried bay leaves 2 sprigs fresh thyme (or 1/2 tsp dried thyme or oregano) Salt and pepper Method Heat oil in a large skillet over medium high heat.</description></item><item><title>Toasted Walnut and Honey Sourdough</title><link>https://www.scottyob.com/recipes/honey-wallnut-bread/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.scottyob.com/recipes/honey-wallnut-bread/</guid><description>Ingredients 100 gram walnuts toasted on stovetop or in oven 1 teaspoon cinnamon 53 grams sourdough starter at its peak 380 grams room temperature water 30 grams raw honey 360 grams bread flour 90 grams all-purpose flour 50 grams whole wheat flour 9 grams sea salt 1 1/2 teaspoons Method Put walnuts on cookie sheet for 6 minutes @ 350f, then toss with cinnamon Mix starter, water, honey, flours and salt After first hour standing mixed, wait at least half an hour before mixing in almonds Notes It&amp;rsquo;s pretty much the same as the basic sourdough but with some differences</description></item><item><title>White Sourdough Bread</title><link>https://www.scottyob.com/recipes/white-sourdough-bread/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.scottyob.com/recipes/white-sourdough-bread/</guid><description>Ingredients 350g of water 500g of bread flour 50g of sourdough starter, fed near it&amp;rsquo;s peak 6-10g of salt Direction Feed starter, have ready for 4pm @ 4pm, place ingredients in a metal bowl, vigerously mix with fork until everything is somewhat combined. Cover (I use plastic bag) and leave on counter @ 5pm, The bread has gone through it&amp;rsquo;s &amp;ldquo;autolyse&amp;rdquo; stage. Start stretching and folding bread into the middle until it feels somewhat firm Every hour or so until bed, keep stretching and folding.</description></item></channel></rss>