<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Scott O'Brien</title><link>https://www.scottyob.com/</link><description>Recent content on Scott O'Brien</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Wed, 10 Nov 2021 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://www.scottyob.com/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Custom Study Desk</title><link>https://www.scottyob.com/posts/custom-desk/</link><pubDate>Wed, 10 Nov 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.scottyob.com/posts/custom-desk/</guid><description>My partner and I recently started renting an old place in Palo Alto. With COVID, we&amp;rsquo;ve been working from home for almost two years now, and sharing a desk at times things felt a little cramped (especially with the occsional electronics project)
I&amp;rsquo;m no expert in woodwork, so decided to 3D model it before building the desk. This also helped as my Father, who&amp;rsquo;s a carpender could give me tips on a shared screen.</description></item><item><title>Paragliding Tasks Checker</title><link>https://www.scottyob.com/posts/paratasks/</link><pubDate>Mon, 20 Sep 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.scottyob.com/posts/paratasks/</guid><description>It&amp;rsquo;s so easy to build react apps these days. Over two nights, I knocked up a quick website to be able to upload igc flight files, and an xctask files to locally compute if you managed to hit the targets.
It&amp;rsquo;s something to play with more later, but I&amp;rsquo;m hoping to start putting these widgets into my logbook app to be able to log flights against tasks when they&amp;rsquo;re done.</description></item><item><title>resuming</title><link>https://www.scottyob.com/2021/09/11/resuming/</link><pubDate>Sat, 11 Sep 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.scottyob.com/2021/09/11/resuming/</guid><description>I&amp;rsquo;ve not been writing or blogging for some time. Over half a decade. It has been about 12 years since I started this blog, and a lot has changed since then. I&amp;rsquo;ve not found the time to document my tinkerings and projects as work has taken most of my time. I&amp;rsquo;m going to leave work related things on Linkedin, personal posts on Facebook, but I would like to continue using this site as my partner tends to use her diaries, as a way looking back at what I&amp;rsquo;ve been playing with.</description></item><item><title>About Me</title><link>https://www.scottyob.com/page/about/</link><pubDate>Tue, 26 May 2020 00:46:16 -0700</pubDate><guid>https://www.scottyob.com/page/about/</guid><description> svg { stroke: currentcolor; fill: none; stroke-width: 2; stroke-linecap: round; stroke-linejoin: round; margin: 1em; height: 3em; } a { }</description></item><item><title>The Bucket List</title><link>https://www.scottyob.com/page/bucketlist/</link><pubDate>Tue, 26 May 2020 00:46:16 -0700</pubDate><guid>https://www.scottyob.com/page/bucketlist/</guid><description>Preface The bucket list started on my website back in February, 2013. The idea was start creating a list of all of the things that I&amp;rsquo;ve accomplished over the years, and keep track of the things that I really want to achieve and experience in my life.
This list is public in the hope others will want to help or experience things with me and help make these happen. This list is ever growing and changing.</description></item><item><title>Very basic MPLS Tutorial</title><link>https://www.scottyob.com/2014/10/02/very-basic-mpls-tutorial/</link><pubDate>Thu, 02 Oct 2014 06:34:14 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.scottyob.com/2014/10/02/very-basic-mpls-tutorial/</guid><description>I made this video a while ago and some people on YouTube seem to like it, so here is my very basic MPLS tutorial. Towards the end of the video there’s a live demonstration showing the concepts with Wireshark</description></item><item><title>Compliance with Cisco IOS Devices &amp; Bulk Changes</title><link>https://www.scottyob.com/2014/07/18/compliance-with-cisco-ios-devices-bulk-changes/</link><pubDate>Sat, 19 Jul 2014 00:11:38 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.scottyob.com/2014/07/18/compliance-with-cisco-ios-devices-bulk-changes/</guid><description>One of the biggest problems in the environment I work in is that almost all of the deployment of our 300+ devices is that everything has been hand crafted. Usually this isn’t such a big problem, but add that with a design decision to route right to the access layer of our campus network with a multi-VRF network and you can start to see how mistakes, or changes in design along the deployment has meant inconsistencies.</description></item><item><title>User Accounting with Netflow</title><link>https://www.scottyob.com/2014/07/08/user-accounting-with-netflow/</link><pubDate>Tue, 08 Jul 2014 05:54:52 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.scottyob.com/2014/07/08/user-accounting-with-netflow/</guid><description>At UOW we had a challenge. We wanted to allow proxy-free internet, but wanted to keep an eye on how much data was being consumed by what sort of users. For this we built Project Herbert http://uowits.github.io/herbert-gui/docs.html.
It uses netflow from inside our network and some syslog monitoring scripts to match up our private RFC1918 address space to the users who have it at that time, process the flows in near-realtime so we can adjust throttling and firewall policy to be reactive with the environment.</description></item><item><title>Logging NAT Translations on the Cisco ASA</title><link>https://www.scottyob.com/2014/05/08/logging-nat-translations-on-the-cisco-asa/</link><pubDate>Thu, 08 May 2014 06:14:09 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.scottyob.com/2014/05/08/logging-nat-translations-on-the-cisco-asa/</guid><description>It’s often handy when dealing with infringement notices and the like to have NAT translations logged. Sure a better way would be to record netflow from these devices (and include the translations) but for a quick syslog solution, you can always:
1 2 3 logging enable logging list ToSyslog level critical logging list ToSyslog message 305011 See http://www.cisco.com/c/en/us/td/docs/security/pix/pix63/system/message/63syslog/pixemsgs.html#wp1054604
Messages will look something like:
1 May 08 13:01:20 freewifi-asa.</description></item><item><title>Finding overlaps in address space</title><link>https://www.scottyob.com/2014/02/24/finding-overlaps-in-address-space/</link><pubDate>Mon, 24 Feb 2014 06:05:36 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.scottyob.com/2014/02/24/finding-overlaps-in-address-space/</guid><description>We have an interesting problem at my workplace, we have an MPLS VPN design for separation of security zones (e.g., staff from students.) and we don’t have MPLS support on our edge. With a L3 to the edge design though this means that while every edge switch has its own address space (per VRF), it also has a /30 uplink (once again, per VRF) back to the PE device.
While this (rightly or wrongly decided) slightly more complicated design in itself isn’t a problem, I’ve been working on programatically putting all of this data into an IPAM (IP Address Management) solution.</description></item><item><title>Automating VLAN changes for ESXi Switchports in Cisco IOS.</title><link>https://www.scottyob.com/2014/01/29/automating-vlan-changes-for-esxi-switchports-in-cisco-ios/</link><pubDate>Wed, 29 Jan 2014 10:51:35 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.scottyob.com/2014/01/29/automating-vlan-changes-for-esxi-switchports-in-cisco-ios/</guid><description>At the organisation I’m currently working for, we recently experienced what appears to be a common issue, VLAN’s trunked down to ESXi nodes were inconsistent.
In our DC, we’re still running the old school Cisco Catalyst switches. If we were running a fabric, or Nexus switches we could put port profiles to action or if we lucky enough to have some equipment running Junos &amp;lt;3 we could be using apply-groups for this.</description></item><item><title>throttling guest internet on Apple Airport Extreme</title><link>https://www.scottyob.com/2013/12/18/throttling-guest-internet-on-apple-airport-extreme/</link><pubDate>Wed, 18 Dec 2013 13:09:03 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.scottyob.com/2013/12/18/throttling-guest-internet-on-apple-airport-extreme/</guid><description>&lt;p>I’ve been happily running my Apple Airport Extreme as m home router for the past few years (since my debian router died, and I’ve been too lazy to replace it).  One of the cool features was the ability to create a guest network (SSID) to access the internet without being able to access your trusted network.  One feature I wanted was the ability to throttle the speed guests can access the internet at.  While I couldn’t do this with the Airport Extreme alone, Add a Juniper SRX100 into the mix that the awesome &lt;a href="http://cooperlees.com" onclick="javascript:_gaq.push(['_trackEvent','outbound-article','http://cooperlees.com']);">Cooper Lees&lt;/a> gave me into the mix and problem solved.&lt;/p>
&lt;p>&lt;a href="https://www.scottyob.com/img/old/2013/12/apple-airport-extreme-base-station_1.jpg" onclick="javascript:_gaq.push(['_trackEvent','outbound-article','http://www.scottyob.com']);">&lt;img class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-362" alt="apple-airport-extreme-base-station_1" src="https://www.scottyob.com/img/old/2013/12/apple-airport-extreme-base-station_1.jpg" width="600" height="450" />&lt;/a>&lt;/p></description></item><item><title>What is Anycast?</title><link>https://www.scottyob.com/2013/04/09/what-is-anycast/</link><pubDate>Tue, 09 Apr 2013 12:15:31 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.scottyob.com/2013/04/09/what-is-anycast/</guid><description>I’ve never found a really simple video on what exactly Anycast is with a basic examples when exploring the concepts. I decided to lab it up and figured this might help some of you starting out with the concepts. Any comments feel free to let me know!
Config Attached for IOS lab HERE.</description></item><item><title>My experiences of managing a Cisco switch with Puppet</title><link>https://www.scottyob.com/2012/12/08/my-experiences-of-managing-a-cisco-switch-with-puppet/</link><pubDate>Sat, 08 Dec 2012 12:19:41 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.scottyob.com/2012/12/08/my-experiences-of-managing-a-cisco-switch-with-puppet/</guid><description>One recent pet gripe of mine has been having to add a new VLAN into our datacenter for our vSphere platform. Not that I trust my DCs switches with puppet just yet, this is a proof of concept post about how we could be using puppet to centrally manage this configuration and push it out across our DC.
Before We’ve got a pretty basic topology going on in our DC, it’s just a VSS with the other switches pretty much being nothing more but layer 2 for the most part.</description></item><item><title>Address Book For the Blind</title><link>https://www.scottyob.com/2012/11/08/address-book-for-a-the-blind/</link><pubDate>Fri, 09 Nov 2012 00:32:51 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.scottyob.com/2012/11/08/address-book-for-a-the-blind/</guid><description>&lt;p>This article is about using the &lt;a href="http://www.asterisk.org" onclick="javascript:_gaq.push(['_trackEvent','outbound-article','http://www.asterisk.org']);">Asterisk PBX&lt;/a> and exploiting &lt;a href="http://www.google.com/insidesearch/features/voicesearch/index.html" onclick="javascript:_gaq.push(['_trackEvent','outbound-article','http://www.google.com']);">Google’s voice recognition &lt;/a>API built for voice search in Chrome to build an address book that technology inept people (my grandmother) can use to place cheap telephone calls over VoIP.&lt;/p>
&lt;p>This tool is built for my grandmother; a lady who has &lt;a href="http://www.mdfoundation.com.au" onclick="javascript:_gaq.push(['_trackEvent','outbound-article','http://www.mdfoundation.com.au']);">macular degeneration&lt;/a> making her legally blind.  She doesn’t want to invest a great deal of money in this solution or have much of a learning curve, it took long enough to get her using the two button audio book solution on the iPod.  &lt;/p></description></item><item><title>ZFS and Apple Time Machine, a perfect team</title><link>https://www.scottyob.com/2012/07/31/zfs-and-apple-time-machine-a-perfect-team/</link><pubDate>Tue, 31 Jul 2012 12:09:51 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.scottyob.com/2012/07/31/zfs-and-apple-time-machine-a-perfect-team/</guid><description>So lately I’ve been thinking about my backup strategy on my Mac. From previous posts you might know I’ve build my OpenIndiana ZFS FileServer. Well, just created a volume and decided to put 300GB to good use to create a time machine on my mac. There is a brilliant guide on how to do it here and suggest you all take a look (Thanks for the awesome guide Marco).</description></item><item><title>Monitoring SRX Chassis Cluster</title><link>https://www.scottyob.com/2012/07/09/monitoring-srx-chassis-cluster/</link><pubDate>Mon, 09 Jul 2012 04:44:35 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.scottyob.com/2012/07/09/monitoring-srx-chassis-cluster/</guid><description>Just finishing off a few things at work this week. We’ve got a few sites around the place where we have HA internet powered by two Juniper SRX100’s. The Two SRX100’s operate in a Chassis Cluster and peer with our ISP using BGP across both active/passive devices.
Below is a little Nagios check script that I wrote to hook into our in-house Nagios monitoring platform. It makes sure the chassis cluster has not failed over operating in a degraded state, and makes sure that there are two BGP peers connected.</description></item><item><title>Easily accessing GeoIP restricted sites in your network.</title><link>https://www.scottyob.com/2012/06/03/easily-accessing-geoip-restricted-sites-in-your-network/</link><pubDate>Sun, 03 Jun 2012 11:05:05 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.scottyob.com/2012/06/03/easily-accessing-geoip-restricted-sites-in-your-network/</guid><description>We all know the problem, some sites are restricted to certain countries based on the IP address you’re using to view them. When trying to access over-seas, some solutions are HTTP proxies, Socks proxies and the like. The problem I have with all of these is that they’re annoying to set up whenever you want to to view the site and I don’t want to have to do that for all my devices (iPad, computer, etc).</description></item><item><title>High Availability WordPress LAMP Stack – Part 2</title><link>https://www.scottyob.com/2012/04/13/ha-software/</link><pubDate>Fri, 13 Apr 2012 08:16:30 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.scottyob.com/2012/04/13/ha-software/</guid><description>Setting up the Software Stack This article is the second in a series (see part 1 here). Please see HA Network for the first part in setting up the network topology to be highly available.
It’s all good having a redundant network design, but putting web servers and the like on our hypervisors doesn’t make them redundant. In the event where there’s a failure on one of our servers, all virtual machines on that server will die.</description></item><item><title>High Availability WordPress LAMP Stack.</title><link>https://www.scottyob.com/2012/04/13/ha-network/</link><pubDate>Fri, 13 Apr 2012 07:27:11 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.scottyob.com/2012/04/13/ha-network/</guid><description>Introduction In one of my last little tasks at work, I was asked to eliminate single points of failure in the software and hardware stack without spending a fortune on hardware or software licenses. During the process of ensuring high availability (HA), I realized that many small companies might have similar need, but with more pressing tasks and limited man hours, without a post that talks about all the issues and solutions in one place, many companies and organisations tend to leave single points of failure living with the chance that they’re not going to fail any time soon.</description></item><item><title>What’s the harm in Google DNS?Performance!</title><link>https://www.scottyob.com/2011/07/02/whats-the-harm-in-google-dns-performance/</link><pubDate>Sat, 02 Jul 2011 14:40:05 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.scottyob.com/2011/07/02/whats-the-harm-in-google-dns-performance/</guid><description>EDIT: It looks like Google has recently starting peering in more places in AU with an anycast solution that fixes these issues.
On a little side note to the tutorial series I’ve been writing up lately for building a ZFS fileserver. This one is about Why Google DNS is bad for your performance (well, depending on where you live) A real quick run down, we all know what DNS does yeah?</description></item><item><title>Allowing access through NFS &amp; SAMBA</title><link>https://www.scottyob.com/2011/04/04/allowing-access-through-nfs-samba/</link><pubDate>Mon, 04 Apr 2011 11:53:32 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.scottyob.com/2011/04/04/allowing-access-through-nfs-samba/</guid><description>Cifs Share CIFS (Common Internet File System), the protocol windows users for all it’s ‘windows file sharing’ is the method I’ll allow for my desktops and roaming computers to access files on the file server.
Before we begin, Make sure we install the CIFS kernal modules
1 # pkg install SUNWsmbs # pkg install SUNWsmbskr next we issue this command to make sure it auto starts</description></item><item><title>3. Setting up FileSystems and Snapshots (part 2)</title><link>https://www.scottyob.com/2011/03/24/3-setting-up-filesystems-and-snapshots-part-2/</link><pubDate>Thu, 24 Mar 2011 18:17:20 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.scottyob.com/2011/03/24/3-setting-up-filesystems-and-snapshots-part-2/</guid><description>Note: This post is one in a series aimed to be a tutorial eventually, it’s not currently finalised and at the moment exists as a place for collating thought and collecting feedback
In part 1 of this blog post, I showed you how I created a script that would, when run, rotate your snapshots on a ZFS filesystem. For this to be usable, we need to create a mechanism for having it be automatically ran.</description></item><item><title>3. Setting up FileSystems and Snapshots (part 1)</title><link>https://www.scottyob.com/2011/03/18/3-setting-up-filesystems-and-snapshots/</link><pubDate>Fri, 18 Mar 2011 12:10:36 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.scottyob.com/2011/03/18/3-setting-up-filesystems-and-snapshots/</guid><description>Note: This post is one in a series aimed to be a tutorial eventually, it’s not currently finalised and at the moment exists as a place for collating thought and collecting feedback
Setting up the FileSystems is a trivial task. First, you can see that when we’ve created a storage pool ‘datastore’ it created a filesystem for us (also called datastore) that can act as a container for child file systems.</description></item><item><title>2. Installing the Operating System</title><link>https://www.scottyob.com/2011/03/16/2-installing-the-operating-system/</link><pubDate>Wed, 16 Mar 2011 11:09:50 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.scottyob.com/2011/03/16/2-installing-the-operating-system/</guid><description>Note: This post is one in a series aimed to be a tutorial eventually, it’s not currently finalised and at the moment exists as a place for collating thought and collecting feedback
Installing OS and setup Network For the following set of posts, I have chosen to use VirtualBox to run through how to use ZFS in building your FileSystem. The first step is downloading and installing OpenIndiana. Get the latest build from http://openindiana.</description></item><item><title>Downloading HTTP in off-peak</title><link>https://www.scottyob.com/2011/01/24/downloading-http-in-off-peak/</link><pubDate>Tue, 25 Jan 2011 00:38:18 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.scottyob.com/2011/01/24/downloading-http-in-off-peak/</guid><description>I want to write a quick and dirty blog post to tell you a little solution on downloading HTTP files in your off-peak usage using linux.
The tools I’ll be using for this is my old favourite wget and a new tool, “at”.
The at daemon is required to be running first, so on debian or ubuntu
/etc/init.d/atd start
Then downloading your file at an off-peak time (4am for me) is as simple as</description></item><item><title>PDF Automator in OSX</title><link>https://www.scottyob.com/2011/01/16/pdf-automator-in-osx/</link><pubDate>Mon, 17 Jan 2011 00:09:46 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.scottyob.com/2011/01/16/pdf-automator-in-osx/</guid><description>As you may have been aware from my previous blog posts, I&amp;#8217;ve been trying to make my life digital, that means any papers I get, I scan and file on a FileServer (with remote backups, etc, etc). My scanner at home has a document feeder on it. The problem is that it doesn&amp;#8217;t do duplex, only a set of sides. So far, I can scan one side of the document, flip the paper of, then scan the back pages.</description></item><item><title>Apple feeling slow?</title><link>https://www.scottyob.com/2011/01/12/apple-feeling-slow/</link><pubDate>Wed, 12 Jan 2011 03:56:47 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.scottyob.com/2011/01/12/apple-feeling-slow/</guid><description>Is your Apple Mac feeling slow? p.s. this is a joke, don&amp;#8217;t actually do it</description></item><item><title>Symfony not sortable in CRUD</title><link>https://www.scottyob.com/2011/01/01/symfony-not-sortable-generate-admin-crud/</link><pubDate>Sat, 01 Jan 2011 12:15:37 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.scottyob.com/2011/01/01/symfony-not-sortable-generate-admin-crud/</guid><description>I&amp;#8217;ve recently come up across some problems with the CRUD generator in Symfony, so in case anyone is googling for a solution out there, I&amp;#8217;ll try and help you along (or at least bump up the page references to the articles that helped me 😉 ) I had a problem today where I was trying to use Symfony&amp;#8217;s (1.4) generate-admin CRUD generator. The issue was that my titles were not sortable when adjusting the fields to display in the generator.</description></item><item><title>Happy New Year – Resolution #1, Network &amp; Data</title><link>https://www.scottyob.com/2011/01/01/happy-new-year-resolution-1-network-data/</link><pubDate>Sat, 01 Jan 2011 12:02:53 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.scottyob.com/2011/01/01/happy-new-year-resolution-1-network-data/</guid><description>It&amp;#8217;s a new year and time to start getting new years resolutions into action. I&amp;#8217;ve moved into my new area in the study so I&amp;#8217;ve started setting it up how I like. The first step is to get my router set up. The router I&amp;#8217;m using is a little &amp;#8216;fit-pc&amp;#8217; box with two ethernet cables. As you can see, it&amp;#8217;s pretty tiny but doesn&amp;#8217;t pack much in terms of power.</description></item><item><title>New Network</title><link>https://www.scottyob.com/2010/12/28/new-network/</link><pubDate>Wed, 29 Dec 2010 00:32:55 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.scottyob.com/2010/12/28/new-network/</guid><description>so I&amp;#8217;ve moved back home with the family now. One thing I&amp;#8217;ve been meaning to do is to digitise my life and get set up on the cloud. I think it&amp;#8217;ll be really basic to start off with. VPN access in to my home network, firewall everything off, then create a few layers of the network. The issue is that I want to go paperless. I want to set up a ZFS Fileserver to store and snapshot all my data with remote encrypted backups of important documents and the like.</description></item><item><title>New upgdate</title><link>https://www.scottyob.com/2010/11/21/new-upgdate/</link><pubDate>Sun, 21 Nov 2010 08:02:09 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.scottyob.com/2010/11/21/new-upgdate/</guid><description>So.. my router/firewall is due for an upgrade (from Lenny to Squeze) Big upgrade&amp;#8230; The following packages will be REMOVED: libdatrie0 libept0 libtorrent10 libxcb-xlib0 mysql-server mysql-server-5.0The following NEW packages will be installed: apache2.2-bin apt-xapian-index autopoint cpp-4.4 dash dbconfig-common diffutils dmsetup firmware-linux-free g++-4.4 gcc-4.4 gcc-4.4-base gconf2 gconf2-common geoip-database gnupg-curl grub-pc insserv install-info isc-dhcp-client isc-dhcp-common iso-codes javascript-common libalgorithm-diff-perl libalgorithm-diff-xs-perl libalgorithm-merge-perl libaprutil1-dbd-sqlite3 libaprutil1-ldap libasound2 libavahi-client3 libavahi-common-data libavahi-common3 libbind9-60 libboost-iostreams1.42.0 libbsd0 libc-bin libc-dev-bin libc6-i686 libcanberra-gtk-module libcanberra-gtk0 libcanberra0 libcroco3 libdatrie1 libdb4.</description></item><item><title>Home networking is back</title><link>https://www.scottyob.com/2010/11/07/home-networking-is-back/</link><pubDate>Sun, 07 Nov 2010 13:09:51 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.scottyob.com/2010/11/07/home-networking-is-back/</guid><description>so, since I had the scare with my Asterisk VoIP box being hacked and a telephone call to Antarctica having being made, I decided to do something about it. My home network now consists of my D-Link Wireless router being put into Bridge mode, with all services pretty much turned off on the thing. My internal network is 10.12.0.0/16. I plan to sub-divide up this address space later, but for now, I&amp;#8217;m pretty much just keeping it in one big heap until I set up my servers and want to separate them further from the wireless workstations, for this reason though, I&amp;#8217;m keeping my setup pretty simple all pretty much in a 10.</description></item><item><title>A dawn of a new Scott</title><link>https://www.scottyob.com/2010/11/07/a-dawn-of-a-new-scott/</link><pubDate>Sun, 07 Nov 2010 10:07:05 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.scottyob.com/2010/11/07/a-dawn-of-a-new-scott/</guid><description>More blogging to come. I saw a movie last night with Rebecca and one of her friends Kat. It was pretty good, we got to see Mark Zuckerberg&amp;#8216;s portrayal in The Social Network. It has made me realise a few things though. I mean, this guy is using open source tools to create some amazing things. I don&amp;#8217;t code half as much as I&amp;#8217;d like to any more.. this is going to change.</description></item><item><title>Backup your site!</title><link>https://www.scottyob.com/2010/10/09/backup-your-site/</link><pubDate>Sat, 09 Oct 2010 14:31:22 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.scottyob.com/2010/10/09/backup-your-site/</guid><description>In my previous post I mentioned how I didn’t back up or migrate any of my data before we stopped paying the hosting company, so it’s all lost.
This has me thinking how much of a shame it would be if I build a wealth of information or a blog that I can use to identify myself and my work, only to have it go if the machine it’s hosted on dies.</description></item><item><title>A new blog</title><link>https://www.scottyob.com/2010/10/09/a-new-blog/</link><pubDate>Sat, 09 Oct 2010 01:30:57 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.scottyob.com/2010/10/09/a-new-blog/</guid><description>Hello everyone. Ok, so this is a brand new blog. What happened to all my old content? I&amp;#8217;d like to say I just wanted to start fresh, but truth is, I was lazy and didn&amp;#8217;t back up any data from my hosting company before my term ended with them.. so I lost my database and content. I&amp;#8217;ll re-post the good stuff, hopefully more in-depth on this site though. Stay tuned. This blog is going to be a lot more personal then my last.</description></item></channel></rss>