<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>routing on Scott O&#39;Brien</title>
    <link>https://www.scottyob.com/tags/routing/</link>
    <description>Recent content in routing on Scott O&#39;Brien</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 02 Jul 2011 14:40:05 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://www.scottyob.com/tags/routing/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>What’s the harm in Google DNS?Performance!</title>
      <link>https://www.scottyob.com/2011/07/02/whats-the-harm-in-google-dns-performance/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 02 Jul 2011 14:40:05 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.scottyob.com/2011/07/02/whats-the-harm-in-google-dns-performance/</guid>
      <description>EDIT: It looks like Google has recently starting peering in more places in AU with an anycast solution that fixes these issues.
On a little side note to the tutorial series I’ve been writing up lately for building a ZFS fileserver. This one is about Why Google DNS is bad for your performance (well, depending on where you live) A real quick run down, we all know what DNS does yeah?</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Happy New Year – Resolution #1, Network &amp; Data</title>
      <link>https://www.scottyob.com/2011/01/01/happy-new-year-resolution-1-network-data/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 01 Jan 2011 12:02:53 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.scottyob.com/2011/01/01/happy-new-year-resolution-1-network-data/</guid>
      <description>It&amp;#8217;s a new year and time to start getting new years resolutions into action. I&amp;#8217;ve moved into my new area in the study so I&amp;#8217;ve started setting it up how I like.  The first step is to get my router set up. The router I&amp;#8217;m using is a little &amp;#8216;fit-pc&amp;#8217; box with two ethernet cables. As you can see, it&amp;#8217;s pretty tiny but doesn&amp;#8217;t pack much in terms of power.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Home networking is back</title>
      <link>https://www.scottyob.com/2010/11/07/home-networking-is-back/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 07 Nov 2010 13:09:51 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.scottyob.com/2010/11/07/home-networking-is-back/</guid>
      <description>so, since I had the scare with my Asterisk VoIP box being hacked and a telephone call to Antarctica having being made, I decided to do something about it. My home network now consists of my D-Link Wireless router being put into Bridge mode, with all services pretty much turned off on the thing. My internal network is 10.12.0.0/16. I plan to sub-divide up this address space later, but for now, I&amp;#8217;m pretty much just keeping it in one big heap until I set up my servers and want to separate them further from the wireless workstations, for this reason though, I&amp;#8217;m keeping my setup pretty simple all pretty much in a 10.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>