<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Personal on Scott O'Brien</title><link>https://www.scottyob.com/categories/personal/</link><description>Recent content in Personal on Scott O'Brien</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Sat, 01 Jan 2011 12:02:53 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://www.scottyob.com/categories/personal/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Happy New Year – Resolution #1, Network &amp; Data</title><link>https://www.scottyob.com/2011/01/01/happy-new-year-resolution-1-network-data/</link><pubDate>Sat, 01 Jan 2011 12:02:53 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.scottyob.com/2011/01/01/happy-new-year-resolution-1-network-data/</guid><description>It&amp;#8217;s a new year and time to start getting new years resolutions into action. I&amp;#8217;ve moved into my new area in the study so I&amp;#8217;ve started setting it up how I like. The first step is to get my router set up. The router I&amp;#8217;m using is a little &amp;#8216;fit-pc&amp;#8217; box with two ethernet cables. As you can see, it&amp;#8217;s pretty tiny but doesn&amp;#8217;t pack much in terms of power.</description></item><item><title>New upgdate</title><link>https://www.scottyob.com/2010/11/21/new-upgdate/</link><pubDate>Sun, 21 Nov 2010 08:02:09 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.scottyob.com/2010/11/21/new-upgdate/</guid><description>So.. my router/firewall is due for an upgrade (from Lenny to Squeze) Big upgrade&amp;#8230; The following packages will be REMOVED: libdatrie0 libept0 libtorrent10 libxcb-xlib0 mysql-server mysql-server-5.0The following NEW packages will be installed: apache2.2-bin apt-xapian-index autopoint cpp-4.4 dash dbconfig-common diffutils dmsetup firmware-linux-free g++-4.4 gcc-4.4 gcc-4.4-base gconf2 gconf2-common geoip-database gnupg-curl grub-pc insserv install-info isc-dhcp-client isc-dhcp-common iso-codes javascript-common libalgorithm-diff-perl libalgorithm-diff-xs-perl libalgorithm-merge-perl libaprutil1-dbd-sqlite3 libaprutil1-ldap libasound2 libavahi-client3 libavahi-common-data libavahi-common3 libbind9-60 libboost-iostreams1.42.0 libbsd0 libc-bin libc-dev-bin libc6-i686 libcanberra-gtk-module libcanberra-gtk0 libcanberra0 libcroco3 libdatrie1 libdb4.</description></item><item><title>A dawn of a new Scott</title><link>https://www.scottyob.com/2010/11/07/a-dawn-of-a-new-scott/</link><pubDate>Sun, 07 Nov 2010 10:07:05 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.scottyob.com/2010/11/07/a-dawn-of-a-new-scott/</guid><description>More blogging to come. I saw a movie last night with Rebecca and one of her friends Kat. It was pretty good, we got to see Mark Zuckerberg&amp;#8216;s portrayal in The Social Network. It has made me realise a few things though. I mean, this guy is using open source tools to create some amazing things. I don&amp;#8217;t code half as much as I&amp;#8217;d like to any more.. this is going to change.</description></item><item><title>A new blog</title><link>https://www.scottyob.com/2010/10/09/a-new-blog/</link><pubDate>Sat, 09 Oct 2010 01:30:57 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.scottyob.com/2010/10/09/a-new-blog/</guid><description>Hello everyone. Ok, so this is a brand new blog. What happened to all my old content? I&amp;#8217;d like to say I just wanted to start fresh, but truth is, I was lazy and didn&amp;#8217;t back up any data from my hosting company before my term ended with them.. so I lost my database and content. I&amp;#8217;ll re-post the good stuff, hopefully more in-depth on this site though. Stay tuned. This blog is going to be a lot more personal then my last.</description></item></channel></rss>