<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Uncategorized on Scott O&#39;Brien</title>
    <link>https://www.scottyob.com/categories/uncategorized/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Uncategorized on Scott O&#39;Brien</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 02 Oct 2014 06:34:14 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://www.scottyob.com/categories/uncategorized/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Very basic MPLS Tutorial</title>
      <link>https://www.scottyob.com/2014/10/02/very-basic-mpls-tutorial/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 02 Oct 2014 06:34:14 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.scottyob.com/2014/10/02/very-basic-mpls-tutorial/</guid>
      <description>I made this video a while ago and some people on YouTube seem to like it, so here is my very basic MPLS tutorial. Towards the end of the video there’s a live demonstration showing the concepts with Wireshark
  </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Compliance with Cisco IOS Devices &amp; Bulk Changes</title>
      <link>https://www.scottyob.com/2014/07/18/compliance-with-cisco-ios-devices-bulk-changes/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 19 Jul 2014 00:11:38 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.scottyob.com/2014/07/18/compliance-with-cisco-ios-devices-bulk-changes/</guid>
      <description>One of the biggest problems in the environment I work in is that almost all of the deployment of our 300+ devices is that everything has been hand crafted. Usually this isn’t such a big problem, but add that with a design decision to route right to the access layer of our campus network with a multi-VRF network and you can start to see how mistakes, or changes in design along the deployment has meant inconsistencies.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Logging NAT Translations on the Cisco ASA</title>
      <link>https://www.scottyob.com/2014/05/08/logging-nat-translations-on-the-cisco-asa/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 08 May 2014 06:14:09 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.scottyob.com/2014/05/08/logging-nat-translations-on-the-cisco-asa/</guid>
      <description>It’s often handy when dealing with infringement notices and the like to have NAT translations logged. Sure a better way would be to record netflow from these devices (and include the translations) but for a quick syslog solution, you can always:
1 2 3  logging enable logging list ToSyslog level critical logging list ToSyslog message 305011   See http://www.cisco.com/c/en/us/td/docs/security/pix/pix63/system/message/63syslog/pixemsgs.html#wp1054604
Messages will look something like:
1  May 08 13:01:20 freewifi-asa.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Automating VLAN changes for ESXi Switchports in Cisco IOS.</title>
      <link>https://www.scottyob.com/2014/01/29/automating-vlan-changes-for-esxi-switchports-in-cisco-ios/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 29 Jan 2014 10:51:35 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.scottyob.com/2014/01/29/automating-vlan-changes-for-esxi-switchports-in-cisco-ios/</guid>
      <description>At the organisation I’m currently working for, we recently experienced what appears to be a common issue, VLAN’s trunked down to ESXi nodes were inconsistent.
In our DC, we’re still running the old school Cisco Catalyst switches. If we were running a fabric, or Nexus switches we could put port profiles to action or if we lucky enough to have some equipment running Junos &amp;lt;3 we could be using apply-groups for this.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>throttling guest internet on Apple Airport Extreme</title>
      <link>https://www.scottyob.com/2013/12/18/throttling-guest-internet-on-apple-airport-extreme/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 18 Dec 2013 13:09:03 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.scottyob.com/2013/12/18/throttling-guest-internet-on-apple-airport-extreme/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;I’ve been happily running my Apple Airport Extreme as m home router for the past few years (since my debian router died, and I’ve been too lazy to replace it).  One of the cool features was the ability to create a guest network (SSID) to access the internet without being able to access your trusted network.  One feature I wanted was the ability to throttle the speed guests can access the internet at.  While I couldn’t do this with the Airport Extreme alone, Add a Juniper SRX100 into the mix that the awesome &lt;a href=&#34;http://cooperlees.com&#34; onclick=&#34;javascript:_gaq.push([&#39;_trackEvent&#39;,&#39;outbound-article&#39;,&#39;http://cooperlees.com&#39;]);&#34;&gt;Cooper Lees&lt;/a&gt; gave me into the mix and problem solved.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;https://www.scottyob.com/img/old/2013/12/apple-airport-extreme-base-station_1.jpg&#34; onclick=&#34;javascript:_gaq.push([&#39;_trackEvent&#39;,&#39;outbound-article&#39;,&#39;http://www.scottyob.com&#39;]);&#34;&gt;&lt;img class=&#34;aligncenter size-full wp-image-362&#34; alt=&#34;apple-airport-extreme-base-station_1&#34; src=&#34;https://www.scottyob.com/img/old/2013/12/apple-airport-extreme-base-station_1.jpg&#34; width=&#34;600&#34; height=&#34;450&#34; /&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>