<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>recipe on Scott O'Brien</title><link>https://www.scottyob.com/categories/recipe/</link><description>Recent content in recipe on Scott O'Brien</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><atom:link href="https://www.scottyob.com/categories/recipe/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Butternut carrot soup</title><link>https://www.scottyob.com/recipes/butternut-carrot-soup/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.scottyob.com/recipes/butternut-carrot-soup/</guid><description>Ingredients 1 medium butternut squash sliced in half and seeds scooped out 2 large carrots chopped into large pieces 1 head garlic 1 shallot halved and skin removed 1 tablespoons olive oil 1/2 cup milk or coconut milk 1-2 cups chicken or vegetable stock Light sprinkle of Chili Flakes Method Preheat oven to 425 Put halves of squash face down with other vegetables (garlic in it&amp;rsquo;s own foil).</description></item><item><title>Toasted Walnut and Honey Sourdough</title><link>https://www.scottyob.com/recipes/honey-wallnut-bread/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.scottyob.com/recipes/honey-wallnut-bread/</guid><description>Ingredients 100 gram walnuts toasted on stovetop or in oven 1 teaspoon cinnamon 53 grams sourdough starter at its peak 380 grams room temperature water 30 grams raw honey 360 grams bread flour 90 grams all-purpose flour 50 grams whole wheat flour 9 grams sea salt 1 1/2 teaspoons Method Put walnuts on cookie sheet for 6 minutes @ 350f, then toss with cinnamon Mix starter, water, honey, flours and salt After first hour standing mixed, wait at least half an hour before mixing in almonds Notes It&amp;rsquo;s pretty much the same as the basic sourdough but with some differences</description></item><item><title>White Sourdough Bread</title><link>https://www.scottyob.com/recipes/white-sourdough-bread/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.scottyob.com/recipes/white-sourdough-bread/</guid><description>Ingredients 350g of water 500g of bread flour 50g of sourdough starter, fed near it&amp;rsquo;s peak 6-10g of salt Direction Feed starter, have ready for 4pm @ 4pm, place ingredients in a metal bowl, vigerously mix with fork until everything is somewhat combined. Cover (I use plastic bag) and leave on counter @ 5pm, The bread has gone through it&amp;rsquo;s &amp;ldquo;autolyse&amp;rdquo; stage. Start stretching and folding bread into the middle until it feels somewhat firm Every hour or so until bed, keep stretching and folding.</description></item></channel></rss>